Guide to the Margaret Flory Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Other Organizations, Series XII
  - NACLA: Klare, Michael, "The Great South Asian War/U.S. Imperial Strategy in South Asia", 1970 (Box 87, Folder 887)
  - NACLA: Miscellaneous, 1969-1972 (Box 87, Folder 888)
  - NACLA: Women's Room, 1971-1973 (Box 87, Folder 889)
  - Pacific Basin Theological Network, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 890)
  - Pacific School of Religion (Graduate Theological Union) (M. Flory, Minister in Residence, Winter 1981): Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 891)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Bay Area Churches (Montclair Presbyterian, etc.), 1981 (Box 87, Folder 892)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Event Announcements, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 1240)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Worship, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 1241)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Faculty Memoranda, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 893)
  - Pacific School of Religion: GTU Center for Women and Religion, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 894)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Registration Materials, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 895)
  - Pacific School of Religion: GTU Directory, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 896)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Evangelion (Journal), 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 897)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Bulletin, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 898)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Shaman Drum Newsletter, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 899)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 900)
  - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Eighth Quadrennial Convention on the World Mission of the Church (M. Flory, Exhibitor), 1964 (Box 88, Folder 901)
  - Princeton Seminary, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 902)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 903)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary: Internationalization of Mission Seminar (M. Flory, Instructor), 1978 (Box 88, Folder 904)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary: Internationalization of Mission Seminar, Student Papers, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 905)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary: Internationalization of Mission Seminar, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 906)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary: Globalization Committee, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 907)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 908)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College (M. Flory, Executive Secretary, Cooperating Committee): General, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 909)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 88, Folder 910)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 911)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 1226)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 108, Folder 1227)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: Correspondence, 1973-1988 (Box 108, Folder 1228)
  - Tokyo Woman's Christian College: 40th Anniversary Album, 1959 (Box 108, Folder 1229)
  - Tunghai University, Taiwan, 1956-1959 (Box 108, Folder 1230)
  - Union Seminary, 1954, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 1231)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia: Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 109, Folder 1232)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia: Reports, 1955-1970 (Box 109, Folder 1233)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia: Annual Meeting, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 1234)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia: Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 109, Folder 1235)
  - United Methodist Church: Board of Global Ministries (Box 109, Folder 1236)
  - University Christian Center, Beirut, Lebanon, 1966-1969 (Box 109, Folder 1237)
  - WARC: World Alliance of Reformed Churches - 23rd General Council, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 1238)
  - World College West, 1975-1978 (Box 109, Folder 1239)
  - CAREE Communicator (Newsletter), 1980-1981, 1988, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 123, Folder 1316a)
  - Commission of the Churches on International Affairs, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1317)
  - Institute of African Women in Religion and Culture, 2003-2004 (Box 123, Folder 1318)
  - NACLA: Report, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 1318a)
  - Westminster Foundation at Ohio University, 1940-1945 (Box 123, Folder 1319)
  - WARC: World Alliance of Reformed Churches-23rd General Council, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 1320)
- Collected Materials, Series XIII
  - Geographical Files
    - East Asia
      - General/Collected Materials
        - General, 1967-1983, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 919-920)
        - China, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 921)
        - Bibliographies, 1967-1979 (Box 89, Folder 921a)
        - Korea, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 921b)
        - Magazine/Newspaper Articles, 1966-1989 (Box 89, Folder 922)
        - China: Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1976-89 (Box 89, Folder 922a)
        - Korea: Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 922b)
        - Papers/Essays, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 923)
        - Christianity and China (Box 89, Folder 924)
        - Diplomatic Relations, 1949-1981 (Box 89, Folder 925)
        - Ting, Bishop K. H., 1976 (Box 89, Folder 926)
        - "Lessons to be Learned from the Experience of Christian Missions in China" (NCCCUSA Study), 1951 (Box 89, Folder 927)
        - China in the Times -- Index, 1976-1977 (Box 89, Folder 928)
        - Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 929)
        - Notes -- M. Flory (Box 89, Folder 930)
        - Korea: Articles, Essays, and Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1974-1987 (Box 124, Folder 1321)
        - Parmar, Samuel, "The Role of the European Expatriate in Asia", n.d. (Box 124, Folder 1322)
      - Events
        - National Leadership Conference on U.S.-China Relations, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 931)
        - Tour, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 932-933)
        - Tour -- Hsinhua News Agency News Bulletin, 15-19 Oct. 1976 (Box 90, Folder 934)
        - Tour -- Anderson, Kenneth NAACP (participant) -- News and writings, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 934a)
        - The Challenge of China Conference, Stony Point, New York, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 935)
        - Presbyterian China Conference, Richmond, VA., 1980 (Box 90, Folder 936)
        - Senior Friends Event, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 937)
        - Spring Tour (M. Flory, co-leader), 1982 (Box 90, Folder 938)
        - Proposed Youth Study Tour, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 939)
        - Pilgrim Church lecture -- PCUSA news clipping, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 939a)
      - Organizations
        - China Panel (NCCCUSA), 1968 (Box 90, Folder 940)
        - Canada China Program, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 941)
        - UPCUSA Program Agency, China Concerns Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 90, Folder 942)
        - UPCUSA Program Agency, China Update, 1981-1989 (Box 90, Folder 943)
        - U.S.-China People's Friendship Association, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 944)
    - Latin America
      - Papers/Articles
        Scope and Contents
        Chiefly from the files of the Office of Student World Relations and/or the Latin America Department of the NCCCUSA
        - Resource Lists, OSWR and LAD (Box 90, Folder 945)
        - "The Brazilian Democracy" (SWR), 1966 (Box 90, Folder 946)
        - "Christians and Social Change in Latin America" (First Latin American Evangelical Consultation on Church and Society), 1961 (Box 90, Folder 946a)
        - Church and Society in Latin America Social Justice Training Project: Report on the Institute for the Formation of Teams of Education for Social Awareness. Conference held in Santiago, Chile, in collaboration with MEC., 1968 (Box 90, Folder 946b)
        - "CIF Reports: The University in Latin America: Three Recent Articles" (LAD), 1966 (Box 90, Folder 947)
        - Comision de Mujeres: Proceso Educativo, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 947a)
        - "Focus: Latin America Bibliography", n.d. (Box 90, Folder 948)
        - "General Propositions of the U.N. Conference on Trade and Development" (LAD), 1964 (Box 90, Folder 949)
        - "Inter-American Myth and Human Reality" (UPCUSA), 1968 (Box 90, Folder 950)
        - "Latin America and the Puebla Conference" (Theology in the Americas), 1978 (Box 90, Folder 951)
        - "Latin American Involvements of the UPCUSA" (SWR), 1964 (Box 90, Folder 952)
        - "Latin American Newsletter" (LAD), 1967 (Box 90, Folder 953)
        - "An Open Letter to North American Christians", n.d. (Box 90, Folder 954)
        - "Protestant History in Latin America" (Brazil, Chile, Guatemala, Mexico, Venezuela) (SWR), n.d. (Box 90, Folder 954a)
        - "Topical Suggestions for Task Force Study Projects" (SWR), n.d. (Box 90, Folder 955)
        - Alves, Ruben, "Latin America in Captivity" (SWR), n.d. (Box 90, Folder 956)
        - Alves, Ruben, "On the Life of the Churches and the Ecumenical Movement in Latin America: an ISAL Position", 1969 (Box 124, Folder 1323)
        - Alves, Ruben, "Priorities for Peace in Inter-American Relations" (SWR), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 957)
        - Assman, Hugo, "The Christian Contribution to the Liberation of Latin America", n.d. (Box 91, Folder 958)
        - Bennett, Edwin G., "University Ministry in Latin America" (Episcopal Church), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 959)
        - Burgos, A. Oramas, "Datos Estadisticos Sobre La Poblacion Universitaria En America Latina", n.d. (Box 91, Folder 960)
        - Campbell, J. Gary, "Latin American Protestants Move Toward Unity and Demand Human Rights", 1978 (Box 91, Folder 961)
        - Carney, Larry S., "Fiefdom and Revolt: Economic and Political Determinism in U.S.-Latin American Relations", 1967 (Box 91, Folder 962)
        - Castillo-Cardenas, Gonzalo, "Christians and the Struggle for a New Social Order in Latin America" (SWR), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 963)
        - Castro, Emilio, "Protestants in the Latin American Revolution" (LAD), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 964)
        - Conteris, Hiber, "The Role of the Church in Social Change in Latin America: A Protestant Appraisal" (SWR), 1965 (Box 91, Folder 965)
        - Couch, Beatriz Melano, "Those Other Americans" (SVM Newsletter) (SWR), 1958 (Box 91, Folder 966)
        - Divas, Luis Armando, "Christian Approach to the Student Movement in Mexico" (SWR), 1959 (Box 91, Folder 967)
        - Draper, Theodore, "Containing Communism" (LAD), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 968)
        - Fals-Borda, Orlando, "The Ideological Biases of North Americans Studying Latin America" (SWR), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 969)
        - Fals-Borda, Orlando, "Promise and Frustration in Social Change" (SWR), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 970)
        - Fitzpatrick, Joseph P., "What Is He Getting At?" (Re: Illich) (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 971)
        - Franco, Leonardo, "The Student Christian Movement in the Latin American University of Today" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 972)
        - Gajardo V., Joel, "The Latin American Situation", 1978? (Box 91, Folder 973)
        - Gerassi, John, "The Cell: A Play", n.d. (Box 91, Folder 974)
        - Gerassi, John, "Latin America: The Politics of Despair", n.d. (Box 91, Folder 975)
        - Green, Dana S., "Ecumenical Perspectives in Promoting Justice and Peace in Latin America" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 976)
        - Green, Dana S., "Protestantism and Higher Education in Latin America" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 977)
        - Henderson, William H., "Concluding Reports: Educational Fellowship in Latin America" (APUP), 1958 (Box 91, Folder 978)
        - Hoffman, Rev. Ronan, "Social Change in Latin America: The Mission of the Church" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 979)
        - ISAL, "An Effort at 'Incarnation'" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 980)
        - Illich, Ivan, "The Seamy Side of Charity" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 981)
        - Krushnic, Richard, "United States Military Bases in Puerto Rico and their Strategic Function", 1968 (Box 91, Folder 982)
        - Larabraud, Jorge, "Revolution in the Western Hemisphere" (Inter-American Dialogue) (SWR, LAD), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 983)
        - Liggett, Thomas J., "Latin America - A Challenge to Protestantism", 1959 (Box 91, Folder 984)
        - Lagged, Thomas J., "The Role of the Missionary in Latin America Today" (LAD), 1963 (Box 91, Folder 985)
        - Lopez, Mauricio, "The Gospel and the Latin American University Community" (SWR), 1962 (Box 91, Folder 986)
        - Lopez, Mauricio, "Report on Christian Student Work in Latin America" (SWR), 1958 (Box 91, Folder 987)
        - Lopez, Mauricio, "Youth Leadership Training Institute in Cuba" (SWR), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 988)
        - Mackay, John A., "The Spiritual Spectrum of Latin America" (LAD), 1965 (Box 91, Folder 989)
        - Oglesby, Carl, "La Bancarrota De Los Liberales" (SWR), 1965 (Box 91, Folder 990)
        - Petras, James, "Carter's Human Rights Policy in Latin America", 1978? (Box 91, Folder 991)
        - Petras, James, "Making South America Safe for U.S. Tourists" (LAD), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 992)
        - Pike, Frederick B. "Church and State in Mid-Century Latin America: A Catholic's View" (LAD), 1965 (Box 91, Folder 993)
        - Plank, John N., "The Alliance for Progress" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 994)
        - Rogers, William W., "Should Brazilians Dream Again of the Promised Land?", 1993 (Box 124, Folder 1324)
        - Shaull, M. Richard, "The Church and Revolutionary Change: Contrasting Perspectives", 1966 (Box 91, Folder 995)
        - Shaull, M. Richard, "National Development and Social Revolution" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 996)
        - Shaull, M. Richard, "The New Revolutionary Mood in Latin America" (SWR), 1962 (Box 91, Folder 997)
        - Shaull, M. Richard, "Recent Studies of Political Developments in Asia, Africa and Latin America" (SWR), 1963 (Box 91, Folder 998)
        - Shaull, M. Richard, "The War of National Liberation -- Next Stage in Latin America?" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 999)
        - Smith, Eugene L., "The Role of Churches in International Affairs" (LAD), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1000)
        - Torres, Sergio, "Puebla 1979: The III Conference of the Latin American Bishops" (Theology in the Americas) (Box 91, Folder 1001)
        - Tyson, Brady, "Latin American Reactions", 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1002)
        - U.S. Conference on Church and Society, "Proposals on Strategies and Tactics" (LAD) (Box 91, Folder 1003)
        - "U.S. Latins Vote Political Drive: Spanish Speaking Unit Plans Office in the Capital" (N.Y. Times), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1003a)
        - Washington, S. Walter, "Student Politics in Latin America: The Venezuelan Example" (SWR), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1004)
        - WCC Exchange (Bi-Monthly Documentation Service) No. 5, "Oppression and Struggle for Justice in Latin America", 1977 (Box 91, Folder 1004a)
      - Presbyterian Involvement in Latin America
        - Program Review of Regional Office for Latin America (COEMAR), 1964 (Box 91, Folder 1005)
        - Presbyterian Consultation on University Work in Latin America (Guatemala), 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1006)
        - Advisory Council on Inter-American Affairs, UPCUSA, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1007)
        - Myth and Reality in Inter-American Relations: Statement, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 1008)
        - COEMAR Regional Strategy Group, 1969-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1009)
        - COEMAR Ad Hoc Committee on Latin America, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 1010)
        - Guidelines for UPC Participation in Mission with Churches in Other Nations, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 1011)
        - Notebook: Latin America Programs, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1011a)
        - Notebook: Latin America Programs; Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1011b)
      - Miscellaneous Materials
        - Committee on Cooperation in Latin America (NCCCUSA) Study Conferences, 1958-61 (Box 92, Folder 1012)
        - Preliminary Consultation: The Church's Task in British Guiana, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 1013)
        - Brazil '65 Project, Cornell University, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1014)
        - Brazil '66 Project, Cornell University, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1015)
        - Dominican Republic: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1015a)
        - Report on the Institute for the Formation of Teams of Education for Social Awareness (ISAL/MEC), 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1016)
        - NACLA Report on the Americas, XXI.4 and XXII.5, 1987, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 1016a)
        - Brazil -- Repression, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 1017)
        - Brazilian Information Bulletin, No. 16, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 1017a)
        - Iglesia y Sociedad En America Latina (ISAL), 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1018)
        - Confession of Faith (Cuba), 1977 (Box 92, Folder 1019)
        - Central America -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1990 (Box 92, Folder 1020)
        - Cuba: English Language Seminar (M. Flory, instructor), 1979 (Box 92, Folder 1021)
        - Cuba -- Notes and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 92, Folder 1021a)
        - Cuba -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1987 (Box 92, Folder 1021b-1021c)
        - Nicaragua -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1993 (Box 92, Folder 1021)
        - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1022)
    - Other
      - General Geographical Files
        - African Theology: Consultation, Makerere University, Kampala, Uganda, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1023)
        - Africa: Miscellaneous, 1961-1993 (Box 93, Folder 1023a)
        - Appalachia, 1976-1977 (Box 93, Folder 1024)
        - Bangladesh, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1024a)
        - Biafra/Nigeria: Student Crisis, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1025)
        - East Timor, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 1025a)
        - Eastern Europe: "The United States and Eastern Europe -- An Ecumenical Blind Spot," C. West, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1025b)
        - Eastern Europe: Czechoslovakia and associated materials, 1968-1991 (Box 93, Folder 1025b1)
        - Ghana: Health Handbook (American Embassy) (Box 93, Folder 1025c)
        - India, 1957-1976 (Box 93, Folder 1025)
        - Indonesia: Kerygma Features, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 1026)
        - Korea: General, 1973-1982 (Box 93, Folder 1027)
        - Korea: Student Crisis, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1028)
        - Korea: Human Rights, 1978-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1029)
        - Korea: Christian Education Resources for U. S. Churches, 1983-1984 (Box 113, Folder 1292h)
        - Korea Church Women United, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 1030)
        - Middle East: COEMAR Response to Middle East Crisis, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 1031)
        - Middle East: University Christian Center Forum Lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 1032)
        - Middle East: International Seminar on Justice and Peace in the Near East, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1033)
        - Middle East: Pilot Project in Higher Education, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1033a)
        - Middle East: General, 1967-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1034)
        - Middle East: General, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 1035)
        - Middle East: Study Tour to Israel with Virginia Hadsell, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 1035a)
        - Philippines: Student Arrests (WSCF), 1979 (Box 93, Folder 1036)
        - Philippines: General, 1974-1989 (Box 93, Folder 1037)
        - Singapore, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 1037a)
        - South Africa, 1967, 1990, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 1038)
        - Thailand, 1976, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 1038a)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence from Missionaries/Abroad (France, India, Poland), 1967-1992 (Box 93, Folder 1038b)
        - Middle East: Miscellaneous Articles and Newsletters, 1979-2003 (Box 124, Folder 1325)
        - South Africa, 1978, 1986, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 1326)
        - Thailand (Box 124, Folder 1327)
  - Topical Files
    - General, Alphabetical
      - Academic Freedom, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 1039)
      - African American Experience (University of Nebraska at Omaha College of Continuing Studies TV Classroom Course), 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1039a)
      - Bibliographies, 1956-1964 (Box 94, Folder 1040)
      - Christianity and Non-Christian Religions (SVM Newsletter), 1959 (Box 94, Folder 1040a)
      - Communism and Christianity, 1949-1965 (Box 94, Folder 1041-1043)
      - Communism and Christianity: "Operation Abolition" (Film) (NCC, NSCF), 1960-1961 (Box 94, Folder 1044)
      - Developing Nations: Manpower (Handwritten Notes) (Box 94, Folder 1045)
      - Development: General, 1967-1976 (Box 94, Folder 1046-1047)
      - Development: Joint Program on World Justice and Development (USCC/NCCCUSA), 1969 (Box 94, Folder 1048)
      - Development: United Nations, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 1049)
      - Disarmament, 1975-1979 (Box 94, Folder 1049a)
      - The Draft, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 1050)
      - Drama: "Drama with a Mission," by M. Flory, Presbyterian Survey, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 1050a)
      - Drama: "The Book of Five Acts," by Robert F. Smylie, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 1050b)
      - Drama: Scripts, Articles, Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 1292b)
      - Drama: Scripts and Services (Box 113, Folder 1292c)
      - Drama: Religious Drama Workshops, Green Lake, WI, sponsored by NCC Div. of Christian Ed. and American Baptist Assembly, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1292)
      - Drama: Articles, Miscellaneous, Lake Geneva Student Conference, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 1292e)
      - Drugs, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 1051)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Orthodox Church, 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 1052)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Orthodox Church, "The Problem of Authority from the Present Perspective," T. Paul Verghese, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 1053)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Presbyterian Church in the U.S., 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 1054)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Protestantism, "Proposal toward the Reunion of Christ's Church," Eugene C. Blake, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 1055)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Roman Catholicism, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1056)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Roman Catholicism, "Dialogue: Worship and Study for Roman Catholic and Protestant", 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1057)
      - Ecumenical Relations: Roman Catholicism, Vatican II, 1962-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1058)
      - Evangelism, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1059)
      - Foreign Policy (NCCCUSA), 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1060)
      - Hunger, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1061)
      - Internationalization, 1965-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1062)
      - Internationalization: Essays, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1063)
      - Internationalization: A Consultation on the Board of Missions and the University World (Methodist), 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1063a)
      - Internationalization: Workshop on International Communities International Consultation, Anderson, Indiana (M. Flory, co-chair), 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1063b)
      - Internationalization: "The University, The Church and Internationalization," by Margaret Flory and Alice Hageman, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1063c)
      - Internationalization: W.U.S. Symposium, Switzerland, "The International Role of the University", 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1063)
      - Internationalization, 1971-1981 (Box 95, Folder 1064)
      - Laity: UPCUSA Staff Consultation, Princeton, N.J. (cf. 53-410), 1960 (Box 95, Folder 1065)
      - Laity: Letter to Laymen, Christian Faith-and-Life Community, Austin, Texas, 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 1066)
      - Language/Cultural Study, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1067)
      - Medicine, 1961, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 1067a)
      - Missionary Strategy: General, 1957-1985 (Box 96, Folder 1068-1071)
      - Missionary Strategy: Agricultural Missions, 1952-1962 (Box 96, Folder 1071)
      - Missionary Strategy: Christian Witness to Islam (WSCF, COEMAR materials), 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 1072)
      - Missionary Strategy: Church Labor Letter (Henry Jones, Japan), 1954-1960 (Box 96, Folder 1073)
      - Missionary Strategy: "Cosmic Dimension of Mission," A.B. Come, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 1074)
      - Missionary Strategy: Industrial Evangelism, 1949-1961 (Box 96, Folder 1075)
      - Missionary Strategy: "The Meaning of Mission," Peter Critchell, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1076)
      - Missionary Strategy: "Missionary Perspective in the Training for the Ministry," M.A.C. Warren, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1077)
      - Missionary Strategy: Missionary Training, 1953-1959 (Box 96, Folder 1078)
      - Missionary Strategy: Moratorium, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1079)